[{"answer": "Hon, I know how busy you are, don't worry about it besides it's a beautiful day to wait. And wait", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Yeah I'm sorry honey I had to, I'm scheduled to be offworld by 1", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Yes dinne", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I'll see you soon", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "What", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "What was what", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Why?", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "No. I want to know why the Aschen doctors looked me in the eye and told me that I was okay. Why did they lie to me?", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "The night before General my friend died he called me and said he needed to speak with me about something very important. Something that he couldn't discuss over the phone.  The next day I told the Ashen doctors, I said this is impossible, he could not have died of a heart attack he was in perfect health, but they said their diagnostic machines were infallible", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "At the time, no, I believed the same as everyone els", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "For us, yes, it was. But with access to Aschen computers..", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "If we don't, then we will live to see the end of the entire human race on that place", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "What are you doing here", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "Which one? We made a few..", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Oh here we go", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Stop this from happening", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "Hey. Thanks for showing", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I'm still thinking about it. In the meantime I took the liberty of doing a little shopping for you", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "All right Let's go", "docId": "Stargate-SG1-2010.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "C'mon. my friend we gotta g", "qsentId": 20}]